<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Issa Sanogo</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Issa Sanogo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Règlement Génnéral sur la protection des Données</title>
      <link>/blog/r%C3%A8glement-g%C3%A9nn%C3%A9ral-sur-la-protection-des-donn%C3%A9es/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/r%C3%A8glement-g%C3%A9nn%C3%A9ral-sur-la-protection-des-donn%C3%A9es/</guid>
      <description>Date de publication : April 17, 2018
Date de dernière mise à jour : May 26, 2018
Introduction Dans un monde de plus en plus tourné vers le numérique, vers les nouvelles technologies, la donnée est une devenue l’or noir du XXIe siècle. Mais depuis le début du siècle, le nombre de cyber-attaque ne cesse d’augmenter. Les révélations d’Ed. Swoden ont ebrallé le monde. Le piratage des 3 milliards de compte de Yahoo et plus récemment l’affaire Cambridge Analityca avec Facebook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m Issa Sanogo. This is my personnel website. For more information about me, go on my homepage or consult my resume.
This blog is about statistics, data in general with a special focus on R and open source software.
As Errare humanum est, some post certainly contain error so please feel free to push a correction request directly on Github.
This site has been created with blogdown and the theme is hugo-sustain, a Hugo theme.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Consulting</title>
      <link>/consulting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/consulting/</guid>
      <description>Get in touch if you have a project in mind. I&amp;rsquo;d love to discuss about it and figure out how I can help you.
Data science You have a data science project but you don&amp;rsquo;t have the time or expertise to complete it? I can help you. Data analysis is a real passion for me. I can also assist you in doing your project by yourself by setting up coaching sessions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/contact/</guid>
      <description>The best way to reach me is by email at ngsanogo@gmail.com. You can contact me about anything but if it&amp;rsquo;s about programming, I advise you to post it on Stack Overflow instead. You&amp;rsquo;ll have all the answers you are looking for and even better answer for sure.
The Kamita association hold events every first Saturday of the month. So if you want to meet me, check on the association&amp;rsquo;s website or on assomaliennes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description>Here are the projects I have worked on or I&amp;rsquo;m working on:
Website This project is about building a website with hugo and blogdown. The source code is hosting on github.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/</guid>
      <description>Pulblished: April 15, 2018
Last update: May 26, 2018
Contact informationEmail: ngsanogo@gmail.com
LinkdIn: Issa Sanogo
Twitter: ngsanogo
Adress: Suresnes, 92150, France
Short biographyI am Issa Sanogo, I am malian.
I am a huge nerd passioned by data science. I love learning and teaching. I am in favor of popularizing sience.
After beeing graduated of bachelor’s degree in Mali I came in France to do my graduate studies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/teaching/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m willing to teach either at university or in private courses.
I think science must not be an occult thing.
I can offer custom R training at your location. if you have a specific need in mind, contact me and we can work on a program together.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>