<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Issa Sanogo</title>
    <link>https://ngsanogo.rbind.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Issa Sanogo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://ngsanogo.rbind.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Règlement Génnéral sur la protection des Données</title>
      <link>https://ngsanogo.rbind.io/blog/r%C3%A8glement-g%C3%A9nn%C3%A9ral-sur-la-protection-des-donn%C3%A9es/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ngsanogo.rbind.io/blog/r%C3%A8glement-g%C3%A9nn%C3%A9ral-sur-la-protection-des-donn%C3%A9es/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Dans un monde de plus en plus tourné vers le numérique, vers les nouvelles technologies, la donnée est devenue l&amp;rsquo;or noir du XXIe siècle. Mais depuis le début du siècle, le nombre de cyber-attaque ne cesse d&amp;rsquo;augmenter. Les révélations d&amp;rsquo;Ed. Swoden ont ebranlé le monde. Le piratage des 3 milliards de compte de Yahoo et plus récemment l&amp;rsquo;affaire Cambridge Analityca avec Facebook. Nous assistons de façon impuissante à de multiples atteintes à l&amp;rsquo;identité humaine, à la vie privée et aux libertés individuelles ou publiques.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://ngsanogo.rbind.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ngsanogo.rbind.io/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m Issa Sanogo. This is my personnel website. For more information about me, go on my homepage or consult my resume.
This blog is about statistics, data in general with a special focus on R and open source software.
As Errare humanum est, some post certainly contain error so please feel free to push a correction request directly on https://github.com/ngsanogo/ngsanogo.rbind.io.
This site has been created with blogdown and the theme is hugo-sustain, a Hugo theme.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Consulting</title>
      <link>https://ngsanogo.rbind.io/consulting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ngsanogo.rbind.io/consulting/</guid>
      <description>Get in touch if you have a project in mind. I&amp;rsquo;d love to discuss about it and figure out how I can help you.
Data science You have a data science project but you don&amp;rsquo;t have the time or expertise to complete it? I can help you. Data analysis is a real passion for me. I can also assist you in doing your project by yourself by setting up coaching sessions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://ngsanogo.rbind.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ngsanogo.rbind.io/contact/</guid>
      <description>The best way to reach me is by email at ngsanogo@gmail.com. You can contact me about anything but if it&amp;rsquo;s about programming, I advise you to post it on Stack Overflow instead. You&amp;rsquo;ll have all the answers you are looking for.
The only social networks I use are : LinkedIn in/ngsanogo and Twitter @ngsanogo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project</title>
      <link>https://ngsanogo.rbind.io/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ngsanogo.rbind.io/projects/</guid>
      <description>Here are some of my projects I have worked on or I&amp;rsquo;m working on:
ngsanogo.rbind.io This project is about building a website with hugo and blogdown. The source code is hosted on github.
corpoaccident The corpoaccident package is a package that contains the data sets on traffic accidents involving injuries in France. The source code is hosted on github.
corpoaccidentdash A Dashbord of traffic accidents involving injuries in France base on the corpoaccident package.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>https://ngsanogo.rbind.io/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ngsanogo.rbind.io/resume/</guid>
      <description>Contact information Email: ngsanogo@gmail.com; LinkdIn: Issa Sanogo; Twitter: @ngsanogo
Short biography N&amp;rsquo;Gouro dit Issa Sanogo is a data manager/Statistican at AP-HP.
He graduated from UFR Math-Info Université Paris DESCARTES, where he obtained a M.S. in mathematical engineering applied to life sciences.
To download his CV, please click here
Education background   2015 - 2017, Master&amp;rsquo;s degree in mathematical engineering applied to life sciences at UFR Math-Info Université Paris DESCARTES, France</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Teaching</title>
      <link>https://ngsanogo.rbind.io/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://ngsanogo.rbind.io/teaching/</guid>
      <description>I can offer custom R training at your location. if you have a specific need in mind, contact me and we can work on a program together.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
